Preliminary Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art archives department records, circa 1890-2007 COR0005.3.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audiovisual and graphics records, circa 1869-2014; 1950-1984; Series 1; 24 Linear Feet
  - Photographs, circa 1890-1984; Series 1 Subseries 1; 37.5 Linear Feet Over 1,353 images
    - A.P. Ryder 1. Watering Place & 2. A Stag Drinking, 1961 April 7-May 14; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Herman Maril, 1961 April 18-May 21; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Picture of the Month - Francis Boucher, Aurora and Cephalus, 1961 May; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Norwegian Exhibition, 1961 October 5-November 5; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folders 60-61)
    - Marian Cannan (Mrs. Arthur Schlesinger) - Friends of the Corcoran, 1961 October 13-November 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Jose Bermudez, 1961 October 17-November 12; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Photos IV-VI The Civil War (nos. 92-170), 1961 November 17-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folders 64-65)
    - Civil War Photos VII-XI (nas. 171-236), 1961 November 31-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Civil War Photos 1-111 (nos. 1-91), 1961 November 17-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Civil War D.G. Blythe, Battle of Gettysburg, 1961 November 17-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Civil War Homer, The Last Goose, 1961 November 17-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Civil War Exhibition, 1961 November 17-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Civil War Photos 1-111 (nos. 1-91), 1961 November 17-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - The Civil War Photos Rejected, 1961 November 17-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folders 72-76)
    - Picture of the Month - Emmanuel Leutze, 1962 January; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 77)
    - 15th Area Show - H.I. Gates, Space Minded and Ready, 1962 January 20; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Fifteenth Area Exhibition, 1962 January 19-February 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 79)
    - John Marin, 1962 March 2-April 15; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 80)
    - John Marin - Laurel Blossones, 1962 March 2-April 15; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 81)
    - John Marin - Maine Islands, 1962 March 2-April 15; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 82)
    - William Calfee, 1962 March 13-April 8; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 83)
    - Picture of the Month - Unknown (School of Lozco) Carvinal Scene, 1962 April; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 84)
    - David Park Retospective, 1962 April 13-May 20; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 85)
    - Edith G. Halpert Collection - Stuart Dans, Landscape, Gloucester, 1962 September 27-November 11; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 86)
    - Edith G. Halpert Collection - Eli Nadelman, The Tango, 1962 September 27-November 11; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 87)
    - Edith G. Halpert Collection - John Marin, Wechawken Sequence, 1962 September 27-November 11; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 88)
    - Halpert Collection Exhibition, 1962 September 27-November 11; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 89)
    - Edith Gregor Halpert Collection, 1962 September 27-November 11; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 90)
    - Edith G. Halpert Collection, 1962 September 27-November 11; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 91)
    - Picture of the Month - Louis M.D. Guillaime, 1962 October; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 92)
    - William Ranney, 1962 October 4-November 11; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 15, Folders 93-94)
    - William Ranney, 1962 October 4-November 11; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folders 1-2)
    - Rudolf Vontlihn, 1962 October 9-November 4; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Picture of the Month - Marsden Hartley, Landscape, 1962 November; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Robert Gates, 1962 November 13-December 9; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Rocakey "Fisilamiento de un comunero" 1962, Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 16 German Painters, 1962 November 27-December 30; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - 16 German Artist, 1962 November 27-December 30; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folders 8-9)
    - Heinz Mack - "16 German Artists", 1962 November 27-December 30; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Picture of the Month 12/1962 J.F. Herring, Fenland Farm, 1962 December; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Ed McGowin, 1962 December 8-1963 January 13; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - CSA Ceramics - Delivery of Equipment, 1962; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Twenty-Eighth Biennial: Barnet-Frasconi, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Twenty-Eighth Biennial: Gatch-Keinbosch, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Twenty-Eighth Biennial: Lewis-Roland, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Twenty-Eighth Biennial: Scarpitta-Williams, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - 28th Biennial: Ilya Bolotowsky, Red and Black Circle, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - 28th Biennial, 1/18/1963-3/3/1963, Maunie Brown, Green Wick, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - 28th Biennial: Steve Durkee, November 35, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - 28th Biennial: Joseph Glasio, Young Lady, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - 28th Biennial: John Hultherg, Cloud Demons, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - 28th Biennial: John Kacere, Interstate, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - 28th Biennial: Ida Kohlmeyer, Opposted, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - 28th Biennial: George McNeil, Gilead, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - 28th Biennial: Walter Murch, Wood Stone Metal, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - 28th Biennial: Raymond Parker, Untitled, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - 28th Biennial: David Peuse, Cascade II, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - 28th Biennial: Gabor Peterdi, Tricket, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - 28th Biennial: Frank Roth, For Diane With Love, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - 28th Biennial: Laurence Warshaw, Cross, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - 28th Biennial: Gerald Winter, Machine for Dispensing Gum Balls, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - 28th Biennial: Jack Youngerman, Red Ripe, 1963 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Picture of the Month - Sarah Grilo, Black Center, 1963 January; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Clare Ferriter, 1963 January 22-February 17; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Picture of the Month - Paul Van Somer, Miss Elizabeth Morrison, 1963 February; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Jacob Kainen - Woman w/ Shawl, 1963 February 26-March 24; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Picture of the Month - Asilia Guillen, Isles of Granda, 1963 March; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Richard Laken - Big Fish, Little Fish, 1963 April 2-June 5; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - New Tradition, 1963 April 26-June 2; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - New Tradition (photos of exhibition), 1963 April 26-June 2; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Picture of the Month - Robert Feke, Dr. Phineas Bond, 1963 October; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Contemporary Painting in Belgium, 1963 October 3-December 1; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Contemporary Paintings of Belgium, 1963 October 3-December 1; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Contemporary Paintings of Belgium - Vic Gentils, Relief, 1963 October 3-December 1; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Contemporary Painting in Belgium, 1963 October 3-December 1; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folders 46-52)
    - Mimi Bolton - Ailegory, 1963 October 8-November 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Pictures of the Month - Unknown, The Minute Man, 1963 November; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Picture of the Month - Rene Magnitte, Les Derniers Beaux Jours, 1963 December; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - 16th Area Exhibit John Chapman Lewis, Oman II, 1963 December 12-1964 February 2; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - 16th Area Show Jacob Karnen, Woman in Blue, 1963 December 12-1964 February 2; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - 16th Area Exhibit Robert Kuhn, Monument to a Minor General + the Emperor Nero, 1963-1964; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - 16th Area Show - Richard Lahey, Footbridge-Ogungust, Maine, 1963-1964; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - 16th Area Show Malihen Afnan Mankouk, Untitled, 1963-1964; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - 16th Area Show Keith Martin, Dramatic Vistas, 1963-1964; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - 16th Area Show Olin Russum, Stoneware Bird Bath, 1963-1964; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - 16th Area Show Maria Wishner, Treasure, 1963-1964; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Sixteenth Area Exhibition, 1963-1964; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folders 64-65)
    - 16th Area Exhibition Jack Perlmutter, 1963-1964; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Corcoran Gallery Window Display, 1963; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - "The Cathedral and the Dark Tides, 1964; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Richard Lafean, 1964 January 21-February 16; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folders 69-70)
    - John Chapman Lewis - Archaic Image, 1964 February 15-March 22; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Gabor Peterdi, 1964 February 13-March 29; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Tony Bader - Red + Yellow, 1964 March 31-April 26; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folders 73-74)
    - Picture of the Month - M. de Vlaminck, La Leale de Foir, 1964 March; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - John Singer Sargent, 1964 April 17-June 14; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folders 76-79)
    - Private World of J.S. Sargeant, 1964 April 17-June 14; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - Washington Collects Contemporary Art, 1964 April 30-May 24; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - Washington Collects Contemporary Art (Friend's Exhibit), 1964 April 30-May 24; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - Picture of the Month - De Chirico, Le Visite Aux Beins Mysterieux, 1964 October; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - Japanese Exhibition, 1964 October 1-November 29; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folders 84-90)
    - Contemporary Japanese Painting, 1964 October 1-November 29; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 91)
    - Japanese Exhibition, 1964 October 1-November 29; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folders 92-94)
    - Lowell Nesbitt, 1964 October 6-November 1; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 95)
    - Alexander Russo, 1964 November 5-December 16; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 96)
    - William Walton, 1964 December 15-1965 January 10; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 97)
    - William Walton, 1964 December 15-1965 January 10; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Art USA: Now, 1964 December 29-1965 January 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Picture of the Month, 1964-1965; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Picture of the Month, 1965 January; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Picture of the Month - Gaber Peterdi, Norfolk IV, 1965 January; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Douglas Teller, 1965 January 19-February 14; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folders 6-7)
    - Picture of the Month - Stanton MacDonald, Old Topango Canyon, 1965 February; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - David L. Kreeger, 1965 February 19-March 28; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - 29th Biennial, 1965 February 27-April 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folders 10-21)
    - 29th Biennial Gene Davis, 1965; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - 29th Biennial Robert Rauschenberg 1st Prize, 1965; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - 29th Biennial, 1965 February 27-April 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folders 24-28)
    - Picture of the Month WM. Malhaerbe, Popples+Anemonies, 1965; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - George L.K. Morris, 1965 May 1-30; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Childe Hassam, 1965 May 1-August 1; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folders 31-47)
    - Romare Beardon, 1965 October 1-31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Picture of the Month Louis Valtat, Personnajes, 1965 October; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Picture of the Month Clay Hagewood, Not too fare from the Yew Tree, 1965 November; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Alfred McAdams Get off the Pad, 1965 November 9-December 5; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Alfred McAdams, 1965 November 9-December 5; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - 17th Area Show David Francke, Vase, 1965 November 12-December 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - 17th Area Show Francis Luzzatto, Rembrandt Meits Simbad in Africa, 1965 November 12-December 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - 17th Area Show Paul Muick, Matrix I, 1965 November 12-December 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - 17th Area Show George O'Connell, Conversations III, 1965 November 12-December 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - 17th Area Show (Garfinckel's Dept/ Store Exhibit) Nov 1965, 1965 November 12-December 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - 17th Area Show, 1965 November 12-December 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - 17th Area Exhibition, 1965 November 12-December 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Picture of the Month, 1965 December; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Pedro San Juan, 1965 December 14-1966 January 9; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folders 51-52)
    - Yugoslavia, 1966 January 7-February 13; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folders 53-61)
    - Paul Reed, 1966 Fanuary 21-February 20; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Op and Pop in Fabric, 1966 January 21-February 20; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Picture of the Month Morris Loius, Untitled 269, 1966 January; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Silver, 1966 February 4-March 6; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Associates Silver Show, 1966 February 4-March 6; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folders 66-68)
    - Picture of the Month Asher Brown Divand Landscape w/a Natural Bridge, 1966 February; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Picture of the Month Maurice Prendergast Portrait of teh Ira Glackewws, 1966 March; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - William Baziotes, 1966 March 11-April 10; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - James Twitty Dover III, II, IV, 1966 March 29-April 24; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Picture of the Month Portrait of the Mr + Mrs David Lynn, 1966 April; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Past and Present, 1966 April 15-September 30; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Past and Present Visitors in the Gallery, 1966 April 15-September 30; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - George Rickey/Kinetic Sculptures, 1966 September 30-November 20; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - George Rickey, 1966 September 30-November 20; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 77)
    - Peter Hird, Portrait of J. Novel Macy 5 years: Friends of the Corcoran, 1966 October 6-30; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 78)
    - Peruvian Painting and Sculpture, 1966 October 28-December 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folders 79-83)
    - Peruvian Painting and Sculpture Ebenth "Magic Gold", 1966 October 28-December 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 84)
    - Peruvian Painting and Sculpture, 1966 October 28-December 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 85)
    - Szyszzo "La Ejecuion De Amacu" Peruvian Painting and Sculpture, 1966 October 28-December 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 86)
    - Peruvian Painting and Sculpture - (Roca Rey Sculpture), 1966 October 28-December 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 87)
    - Galdos Rivas "Pintura Mistica" - Peruvian Painting and Sculpture, 1966 October 28-December 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 88)
    - Gatson Garreand "Untitled #7" 10/28-12/18/66 Peruvian, 1966 October 28-December 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 89)
    - C. Galvez - Peruvian Painting and Sculpture, 1966 October 28-December 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 90)
    - Miliver Catahuarinca - Peruvian and Sculpture, 1966 October 28-December 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 91)
    - Thomas Downning, 1966 December 6-1967 January 8; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folders 92-94)
    - 3 Self Taught Artists, F. Penn - Kane, 1967 January 13-February 26; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 95)
    - 30th Biennial, 1967 February 24-April 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folders 96-102)
    - 30th Biennial (installation photos), 1967 February 24-April 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 103)
    - 30th Biennial not exhibited, 1967 February 24-April 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 104)
    - 30th Biennial: Invited Section, 1967 February 24-April 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 30th Biennial, 1967 February 24-April 19; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folders 2-3)
    - Australian Paintings, 1967 March 10-April 16; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folders 4-6)
    - The Australian Painters, 1967 March 10-April 16; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Richard Woodville, 1967 April 21-June 11; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Woodville: Photos Separated from Loan Forms, 1967 April 21-June 11; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Woodville: Separated from Publicity, 1967 April 21-June 11; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folders 10-11)
    - Jules Outski: Beyond Bonds, 1967 April 28-June 11; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Jules Outski, 1967 April 28-June 11; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folders 13-16)
    - Harold Isen, 1967 May 9-June 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Walter Murch Retrospetive, 1967 September 22-October 22; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Playground Sculpture Competition, 1967 October 11-31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - 18th Area Show Barclay Shears - The Harbor Watcher, 1967 November 18-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - 18th Area Show Thomas Downing Seven, 1967 November 18-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - 18th Area Show James Illeary - Untitled, 1967 November 18-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - 18th Area Show - Jurors Viewing Work, 1967 November 18-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - 18th Area Show, 1967 November 18-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - 18th Area Exhibition Photos, 1967 November 18-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - 18th Area Show, 1967 November 18-December 31; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Swedish Exhibition rejected artists, 1968 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folders 27-28)
    - Swedish Exhibition, Photographs, 1968 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folders 29-33)
    - Sweden today: Paintings & Sculpture, 1968 January 18-March 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Colin Greenfly, 1968 January 27-February 28; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folders 35-36)
    - Colin Greenfly, Wishbone, 1968 January 27-February 5; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Clarence John Laughlin - Kimball Mansion, 1968 March 3-April 14; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Al Held, 1968 March 15-April 21; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folders 39-40)
    - Al Held - Greek Garden, 1968 March 16-April 21; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Adolph Gottlieb, 1968 April 26-June 21; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Terud Hara, 1968 April 26-June 21; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Sun Ra Exhibition, 1968 August 19-September 9; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Washington 1968: New Painting, 1968 September 27-November 3; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - John McLauglin - lenders, 1968 November 15-January 10; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - 31st Biennial: Photos & Transport, 1969 February 1-March 16; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folders 47-51)
    - 31st Biennial: Works of Art, 1969 February 1-March 16; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - 31st Biennial: photos, 1969 February 1-March 16; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folders 53-55)
    - 31st Biennial: Museum sharing, 1969 February 1-March 16; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Leon Berkowitz - photos, 1969 February 21-March 23; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Leon Berkowitz - Photos, 1969 February 21-March 23; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Norman Bluhm, 1969 March 21-April 13; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - John Storr Exhibit Catalogue, 1969 May 2-June 9; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folders 60-61)
    - Thomas Eakins - Arcadia, 1969 May 3-June 10; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Installation of Thomas Eakins, 1969 May 3-June 10; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Thomas Eakins, 1969 May 3-June 10; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Thomas Eakins - photos of work, 1969 May 3-June 10; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Thomas Eakins - negatives, 1969 May 3-June 10; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - G. Lee Exhibition, 1969 October 3-November 8; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Robert Morris Unused Photos, 1969 November 23-December 28; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 19, Folders 2-4)
    - Robert Morris Photographs, 1969 November 23-December 28; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 19, Folders 5-8)
    - Morris - Catalogue - Photos, 1969 November 23-December 28; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 19, Folders 9-13)
    - Joseph Shannon Exhibit Photos, 1969 November 21-December 28; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 19, Folders 14-15)
    - H. Marc Moyens Collection, 1969 December 12-1970 January 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Moyens - Photos and Negatives, 1969 December 12-1970 January 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Moyens - Catalog Photos, 1969 December 12-1970 January 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 19, Folders 18-20)
    - H. Mark Moyens Exhibition, 1969 December 12-1970 January 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Moyens: Catalog Transporation and Negatives, 1969 December 12-1970 January 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Mark Moyens Exhibitions, 1969 December 12-1970 January 18; Series 1 subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 23)